James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 20: May 2011 Accession, 1994-2010; 32 boxes
  - Speeches, 1994-2002; 12 boxes (Box 290, Box 291, Box 292, Box 293, Box 294, Box 295, Box 296, Box 297, Box 298, Box 299, Box 300, Box 301)
  - Events, 1998-2010; 20 boxes (Box 302, Box 303, Box 304, Box 305, Box 306, Box 307, Box 308, Box 309, Box 310, Box 311, Box 312, Box 313, Box 314, Box 315, Box 316, Box 317, Box 318, Box 319, Box 320, Box 321)
- Series 21: May 2015 Accession, 1997-2005; 9 boxes
  ML.2015.016
  This series includes records from Baker's time working with the United Nations Mission for the Referendum in Western Sahara.
  Materials in this accession have been arranged into three subseries: Correspondence and Reports, Write in Campaigns, and Meeting Notes. The order in which these materials were sent to Princeton has been maintained.
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1997-2005; 7 boxes (Box 322, Box 323, Box 324, Box 325, Box 326, Box 327, Box 328)
  - Write in Campaigns, 1997-1998; 2 boxes (Box 328, Box 329)
  - Write in Campaigns, 2000-2003; 1 box (Box 330)
- Series 22: Microfilms, undated; 9 boxes (Box 332, Box 333, Box 334, Box 335, Box 336, Box 337, Box 338, Box 339, Box 340)
  ML.2018.019
  This series includes microfilms of materials in the collections.
  Microfilms are arranged by reel number.